learnhub.com 2012-09-23

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the information, as part of the normal operation of our services, we collect from you and what may happen to that information.

Your privacy is very important to us. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information.

By accepting the Privacy Policy and [Service Agreement](http://learnhub.com/service_agreement) in registration or by visiting and using the Site, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the [LearnHub Service Agreement](http://learnhub.com/service_agreement).

### A Special Note About Children

Persons under the age of 13 are not eligible to use the Site. If you are 13 are over but under the age of 18, you may use this Site and submit personal information to us only in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians.

### Information We Collect

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information from you is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience safer and easier. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

In general, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to use our Site, we may require you to provide contact and identity information, billing information, and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the Site. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature.

We use your credit card information to verify the accuracy of your name, address, and other information, as well as to bill you for your use of our services. In addition, under some circumstances, we may ask you for your credit card information or other additional financial information to validate your identity. We do not store credit card information.

We automatically track certain information about you based upon your behaviour on our Site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.

"Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. At present we only use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session, but in the future we may also use data collection devices, including cookies, on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety, to offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie and to allow us to provide information that is targeted to your interests.

You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our Site and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session.

If you choose to buy or sell on the Site, we collect information about your buying and selling behaviour. We also collect other users' comments and ratings about you, any course and tutor offerings you provide on the Site and any other content you provide on the Site, in our feedback area.

If you choose to post comments to lessons, discussions and other areas of the Site, or leave feedback for other users, we will collect that information that you provide to us. We retain this information for the benefit of the Site—more information is available in the [LearnHub Service Agreement](http://learnhub.com/service_agreement).

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

### Our Use of Your Information

We use your personal information to facilitate the services you request. We use personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site to: resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; bill any amounts due from you; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our [Service Agreement](http://learnhub.com/service_agreement); and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection, use or disclosure. At times we look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your personal information to identify users using multiple User ID's or aliases. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.

We may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze Site usage, to improve our content and product offerings, and to customize the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site.

You agree that we may also use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the [Service Agreement](http://learnhub.com/service_agreement) and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications on your account preferences page. You may make changes to your account preferences at any time.

### Our Disclosure of Your Information

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. However the following describes some of the ways that your personal information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business to provide our services.

Advertisers. We aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personal information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. Certain information, such as your name, email address, password, and financial information are not disclosed to these third parties in a personally identifiable manner without your explicit consent.

LearnHub Communities. Your Username is displayed throughout the Site, and is therefore available to the public. All of your activities on the Site will be identifiable to your User ID. Other people can see your published content including lessons, tests, trivia questions, comments, courses and tutor offerings, your authority and so on. Therefore, if you associate your name with your User ID, the people you have revealed your name to will be able to personally identify your LearnHub activities. We also provide a number of ways to allow other users to find out more about you and your Site activities through the authority feature. Further, we may send out notices to you or other community members regarding suspicious activity or policy violations on the Site.

Educational Institutions. We periodically operate programs to collect and provide to educational institutions personally identifiable information about our members and other visitors to this Site who opt-in to this service. Where we do so, this purpose is described on the page of this Site where that information is collected, this information is only collected from persons who have opted-in to the collection, and we identify the educational institutions to which the information may be provided. We generally have agreements with the educational institutions to which we provide the collected information under which they agree to use it only for the purpose of soliciting new applicants to their institutions and only in compliance with laws applicable to them, and to maintain the confidentiality of this information and disclose it only in accordance with their privacy policies generally applicable to their own applicants, but we cannot control and are not responsible for their actions. For more information about the privacy policies of these educational institutions, please visit their websites.

### Legal Requests.

LearnHub cooperates with law enforcement inquires, as well as other third parties, to enforce laws such as intellectual property laws, fraud and other laws, and to help protect you and the LearnHub community from others. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, province, telephone number, email address, UserID history, fraud complaints, and bidding and listing history without a subpoena. However, in an effort to balance your right to privacy and the ability to keep our community functioning properly, we will not disclose additional information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or similar legal procedure, except when the additional disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss.

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. In some cases, personal information that we collect may be stored or processed outside of Canada, and may therefore be subject to the legal jurisdiction of those countries.

Your Use of Other Users' Information

In order to facilitate interaction among all LearnHub community members, our Site provides you with limited access to other users' contact information. For example, as a teacher you may have access to the User ID, email address and other contact information of students, and as the student you may have access to the User ID, email address and other contact information of the teacher.

By entering into our [Service Agreement](http://learnhub.com/service_agreement), you agree that, with respect to other user's personal information that you obtain through the Site, LearnHub hereby grants to you a license to use such information only for: (a) LearnHub-related communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages, (b) any other purpose that a such user expressly agrees to after you tell them the purpose you would like to use it for. In all cases, you must give users an opportunity to remove themselves from your database and a chance to review what information you have collected about them. In addition, under no circumstances, except as defined in this Section, can you disclose personal information about another user to any third party without our consent and the consent of that user. You agree that other users may use your personal information to communicate with you in accordance with this Section. Note that law enforcement personnel, and other rights holders are given different rights with respect to information they access.

LearnHub and our users do not tolerate spam. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, you are not licensed to add a LearnHub user, even a user who has purchased content or services from you, to your mail list (email or physical mail) without their express consent. To report LearnHub related spam to LearnHub, please email us at [violations@learnhub.com](mailto:violations@learnhub.com).

### Use of Email tools

You may not use the Email to a Friend service or other email services that we offer to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our [Service Agreement](http://learnhub.com/service_agreement). We do not permanently store email messages or the email addresses sent from these tools.

If you do send an email using the Email to a Friend service to an email address that is not registered on our Site, we do not use that email address for any purpose other than to send your email. We do not rent or sell these email addresses.

### Control of Your Password

You are responsible for all actions take with your User ID and password, including fees incurred by your account. Therefore, we do not recommend that you disclose your LearnHub password to any third parties. If you choose to share your User ID and password or your personal information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions take with your account and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy before doing so. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password by going to your account page.

Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information

Following registration, you can review and change the information you submitted during registration including:

  1. Your User ID and email address. If you change your User ID we keep track of your old User ID(s) and your new User ID.
  2. Your name, city, province, country, gender, interests, work history, education history, your picture, and your password.

You must promptly update your information if it changes. Once posted, you cannot change or remove any public comments made on lessons, discussions or other reviews of course and tutor offerings.

Upon your request, we will deactivate your account and contact information from our active databases. To make this request, please send us an email at support@learnhub.com. Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible based upon your account activity and in accordance with our deactivation policy and applicable law.

We will retain in our files some personal information you have requested to remove to prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our [Service Agreement](http://learnhub.com/service_agreement) and comply with legal requirements as is permitted by law. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personal information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. However, such personal information will be deactivated from public and member viewing and will only be available to select LearnHub personal.

### Other Information Collectors

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are teachers or students on our Site or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. Since LearnHub does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

### Security

LearnHub uses procedural and technical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft, as well as against unauthorized access or disclosure, to protect your privacy, including firewalls and encryption. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.

### Privacy Tools

It is our goal to make our privacy practices easy to understand. If you have questions or if you would like more detailed information, please email us at [support@learnhub.com](mailto:support@learnhub.com).

### Notice

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on the Site. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on the Site. In addition, we will notify you in accordance with your Notification Preferences and the [Service Agreement](http://learnhub.com/service_agreement).
